Jude Lim (Ken Yoong)

MS in Computer Science and Applications

Email:

lkyoong428@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jud

e-lim-9a2612101/

Mobile:

+1703-679-0990

Github:

LinkedIn:

https://github.com/KenLim4337/

Location:

Falls Church, VA

I am a master's student in Computer Science and Applications at Virginia Tech focusing on Human Computer Interaction, Data Analytics and Machine Learning. My passions lie in developing and designing interfaces that put the user first

I also have over 3 years of front-end development experience in building, maintaining and testing responsive A/B tests for businesses both big and small. With a well-developed skill set centered around web technologies and UX, I am looking for exciting opportunities to further grow as a developer.

Skills

Hard Skills

Front End Web Development, Conversion Rate Optimization, User Acceptance Testing, A/B Testing, Web Analytics, Back End Web Development, User Experience

Soft Skills

Teamwork, Problem-solving, Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Adaptability

Technologies

Web Technologies - HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, Javascript, jQuery, React, Django, PHP Data and Analytics - MySQL, PostgreSQL, R, Python, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager A/B Testing - Optimizely, VWO, Oracle Maxymizer, Google Optimize, AB Tasty Design Tools - Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Invision, Figma, Balsamiq Other Programming Languages - Java, C#, C, Python Version Control - Git, Subversion

Languages

English(Native), Mandarin(Intermediate), Cantonese(Intermediate), Bahasa Melayu(Intermediate)

Professional Experience

Conversion Rate Optimization Developer

Conversion Kings (Australia)

Increased conversion rates and revenue for over 40 national and international brands through the development, maintenance and analysis of over 250 A/B tests and web-pages.

- Developed pixel-perfect, responsive, cross-browser A/B tests and web-pages based on prototypes provided by designers.
- Reduced project turnaround time and missed bugs by 30% within the first half-year by implementing a standardized user acceptance testing process and managing the team surrounding it.
- Slashed training times for various processes by 50% by writing manuals to help on-board new team members.

Freelance Web Developer

March 2020 - May 2020

February 2018 - July 2021

Dance Sydney (Australia)

Designed and developed a cross-browser, fully responsive video player used to deliver online dance courses to users.

Gliding Queensland (Australia)

November 2017

Streamlined the website redesign process by fixing existing issues and compiling recommended updates based on user experience principles.

Documented website functions to help existing members easily access and modify published content.

April 2017 - October 2017

Code Camp (Australia)

Cooperated with other team members to deliver engaging and organized coding lessons to primary school children.

• Lessons were delivered on-schedule and well-received by both children and parents.

Intern

December 2015 - February 2016

KPerak Implementation and Coordination Corporation (Malaysia)

Delivered a full-stack project in the form of an internal employee assessment web application.

Project completed 2 weeks ahead of schedule and subsequently deployed with minimal rework.

Volunteer Experience

GovHack 2017 July 2017

Hacker & Crew (Australia)

Received honorable mention for the "Going places" national award category by developing a mobile web application.

- Application developed through the usage of various publicly available datasets.
- Made sure participants were hacking in a safe and comfortable environment by helping set up the event location, providing technical support and preparing meals.

Gliding Queensland

March 2017 - November 2017

Volunteer (Australia)

Constructed a framework for the client's redesign efforts by providing feedback based on design and development best practices.

• Client was very positive toward the work delivered and at the end of the year, received a short term contract to further aid the redesign.

GovHack 2016 July 2016

Hacker (Australia)

Won runner-up for the "Evacuation - help us get away!" state award category through collaborating with other participants to ideate and produce a mobile web application using publicly available datasets.

Coder Dojo Brisbane March 2016

Volunteer (Australia)

Along with other team members, taught high school students various coding basics and principles.

• Lessons delivered on schedule and effectively with positive receptions from both students and parents.

Education & Training

2021 - Current

Master of Science in Computer Science and Applications, Virginia Tech

2020

Advanced Google Analytics, Google Analytics Academy Google Tag Manager Fundamentals, Google Analytics Academy

2019

15.071x The Analytics Edge, MITx on edX
Google Analytics for Beginners, Google Analytics Academy

2017

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honours), University of Queensland

2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Information Technology, University of Queensland

Hobbies and Interests

Cooking, Reading, Electronics